♪ Why did you invite me again? ♪
♪ Without good wine, the old immortal won't come ♪
[What If It's Funny?]
[The East New Town project has started!]
Mr. Rong.
I've
brought the master here.
What master?
The one I recommended to you last time.
He's an expert in geomancy.
Mr. Zhou.
Today,
I'm here to bring you wealth.
To bring me wealth?
Exactly.
Do you think
I'm short of wealth?
The wealth is not brought by me.
It's this.
I brought this specially for you.
This God of Wealth...
This God of Wealth is not ordinary.
After my forty-nine...
[The East New Town project has started!]
[Fang Yong, Director of the Administrative Committee of the East New Town]
Interesting.
Master, where
should I place this?
Master.
Don't speak.
I'm looking for the spot.
Usually, the God of Wealth
sits in the north and faces the south.
This one is different.
Let it sit in the east.
Just place it there.
♪ Why did you invite me again? ♪
[East New Town]
♪ Without good wine, the old immortal won't come ♪
[The East New Town project has started!]
[Fang Yong, Director of the Administrative Committee of the East New Town]
[East New Town]
[Born with Luck]
[Episode 4]
[Sanjiangkou Transportation Center]
Bro, who exactly are we going to target?
Bro.
That's the hardest part.
Our target is a corrupt official,
and it has to be a big one.
But how to determine
who the big corrupt officials is
is a thorny issue.
Over the years, those who
were extremely corrupt
and well-known among the people
have all been arrested.
The ones left are of course
extremely low-key and cautious.
So who exactly is it?
Bro, you haven't said yet.
How do we find this person?
Let's draw a profile of him.
I'll go get a pen from the car.
No need for a pen.
Since the person
is a big corrupt official,
their rank can't be low.
Though those clerks
sitting at the service windows
are so proud of themselves
when selecting a romantic partner
that they act highly arrogant,
they...
Secondly,
the person must have been in a position
of real power
for a number of years.
Otherwise, even if the person
is a big corrupt official,
with limited time,
they can't embezzle much money.
Finally,
the person has to be over forty.
Do you know why?
Why?
Because only older corrupt officials
would be foolish enough
to hide the embezzled money and things
in their homes.
Who is it?
Let's go.
There's a man over there staring at me.
Could he be a cop?
We can't take the coach.
Who is it?
Bro.
Chief, where are we going?
To the train station.
Why the train station?
Wouldn't they take a coach?
I'm sure they'll go to the train station.
Why?
It's an investigator's intuition.
[The East New Town project has started!]
[Fang Yong, Director of the Administrative Committee of the East New Town]
What did you just say?
"What's wrong, bro?"
The sentence before that.
"Who is it?"
The East New Town project has started.
The director
of the administrative committee
is Fang Yong.
Excuse me, excuse me.
[Police]
Excuse me.
Stop. Who are you?
Hello.
W-We are police officers
from Sanjiangkou City,
members of a CID branch.
You are police officers, right?
Yes.
We have an important witness to find.
Please
register here.
Okay.
Thank you.
[Police]
Alright, you can go in.
Okay.
Chief!
Chief.
One, two, go.
Where, where?
How do we get in?
They are cops.
Yes.
It's okay, it's okay.
Li Feng.
Don't do it again.
Jiang Ying.
Last night,
you delivered the takeout to me,
right?
Yes.
Yesterday at your house,
seeing your police uniform,
I knew you were a cop.
Yes, I am.
Don't...
I told you, she delivered it.
We found her.
Come at me.
I killed them all.
It has nothing to do with her.
Li Feng.
Stop it.
I don't want to escape anymore.
Think about our child.
It's fine.
We hid in Sanjiangkou
for over half a year.
We thought we were safe.
But I had a bad feeling last night.
You were checking for drunk driving,
even on non-motorized vehicles.
You were looking for me, weren't you?
I didn't expect
you to find us today.
Fine.
Debts owed
must be paid sooner or later.
I admit defeat.
Ren.
Master, what's up?
Well, there's no one else here.
Nobody else is here, Ren.
Come here.
Say it.
No, this thing,
Zheng Yongbing bought it
for only 60,000 yuan.
You said
it cost 160,000.
How much?
160,000 yuan.
How much should I pay you?
60,000 yuan.
Then you quoted Mr. Zhou
260,000 for it.
What do you mean?
I was wondering
if you could pay me a little more.
You are just an extra.
80 yuan per day.
How much did I pay you?
1,000 yuan.
Where's your conscience?
Don't be too greedy.
How about your professional ethics?
Well, what conscience?
Ren.
I nailed it in one take just now.
My professional skills are exceptional.
I will give you another 500.
Get out of here.
Okay.
Thank you, Ren.
Li Penggai.
Come here.
Brother Ren, I was looking for you.
Do you have 500 yuan?
[Li Penggai, Head of the Security Team of Rongcheng Group]
Just 500.
Almost enough.
That's all.
One more word,
and you'll prepare for your own funeral.
Let's go.
Speak.
Ye Jian is dead.
Dead?
How did he die?
Who killed him?
Ren,
what I got earlier is about enough.
I will leave first.
[Fang Yong]
Mr. Rong.
Jianren.
Come and look.
Look.
Does Fang Yong
look like this God of Wealth?
He does.
Look carefully.
So lifelike.
Mr. Rong.
Come out with me.
I need to tell you something.
Just say it here.
Let's talk outside.
Hurry up.
Hurry.
Wait, what are you doing?
Is the sky falling?
Mr. Rong.
Please
take your medicine first.
Without water?
Say it.
My condolences.
My third uncle died, right?
No?
Well, who died?
It's not a big deal. Why...
Why did you give me this medicine?
There's no need.
Who? Tell me.
Y-Ye Jian.
Captain Ye is dead.
Dead?
Yes.
Ye Jian...
He's dead.
Nonsense.
That's impossible.
I didn't believe it at first either.
I just went to confirm it.
Last night,
he was killed.
S-Say it again.
He was killed last night.
Think about who he was.
Who would dare to hurt him?
The police are investigating.
Do you know who did it?
Do you?
We will find out.
Leave. Just leave.
Stop lingering in front of me. Go!
Get out!
Jianren.
Get the sharks
to stop moving!
Okay.
Stop moving!
Mr. Rong, they...
Mr. Rong!
They're sharks!
Where are the people?
Come here!
Mr. Rong.
Are you okay?
[Sanjiangkou People's Hospital]
[Orthopaedics Department] [Orthopaedics Section 1]
My leg got hurt.
What are you crying out for?
Well, you...
Here.
Okay.
I'm fine.
I'm really fine.
Have a seat.
[Orthopaedics Department] [Orthopaedics Section 1]
Please wait a moment.
I'll go get the X-rays.
Go ahead.
Hello.
Hello, Chief.
Li Feng has confessed to everything.
Confessed to what?
This Li Feng,
over the past three years,
has committed over a dozen robberies.
Among them, nine involved murder,
one attempted murder,
resulting in fifteen deaths in total.
He started to hide in Sanjiangkou
half a year ago.
How many deaths?
Fifteen.
Chief.
He is a Class A wanted criminal.
For three consecutive years,
the bureau has issued
a priority arrest warrant for him.
Across five provinces,
tens of thousands of police officers
have been deployed to catch him.
Several times,
he was almost caught.
So close.
But he managed to escape every time.
This time,
you finally caught him.
Chief?
Chief, are you listening?
[Orthopaedics Department] [Orthopaedics Section 1]
Are you sure it's him?
The fingerprints match.
There's no doubt.
The interrogation is still ongoing.
Chief Qi and Captain Wang
are both keeping an eye on it.
Good. Then,
thanks for your hard work.
Keep interrogating him for now.
[Interrogation Room]
[Orthopedic Section 1]
That's quite an achievement.
This is a year ahead of schedule,
and I've overfulfilled the task.
Does this mean
I can go back to the provincial capital?
Chief.
Why are you standing up?
Well.
I was just sitting here,
and suddenly
my whole leg cannot be felt.
It's numb.
Is it that serious?
Look,
I really can't feel it.
You have to keep taking the medicine.
And you
should stay positive.
In your daily life,
watch more funny jokes,
cross-talks, sketches,
or comedy movies.
He's been watching them.
Your vital signs
are all quite stable.
Do you feel uncomfortable anywhere else?
It hurts.
What did you say?
Speak louder.
My arm hurts!
Arm.
His arm hurts.
How about
you take him to orthopedics downstairs?
Okay.
Doctor,
is he okay?
His bones are fine.
I'll just prescribe some medicine for him.
Okay.
Then could there be
some neurological problem?
Right now, not only
does my whole leg hurt,
it's also numb.
How about I get one of those
full body checkups
to examine my body carefully?
Theoretically, it's not necessary.
I don't think it's anything serious.
Don't you trust
what the doctor says?
She said theoretically.
But my whole leg actually hurts.
How about I go back to
the provincial hospital for a checkup.
After all, the medical facilities here...
[Sanjiangkou People's Hospital Radiology Report]
If you don't trust our hospital,
you can go to another one.
Are you his family?
How about
you take him to the fourth floor?
The psychiatry department
might be able to cure his illness.
[Psychiatry Department]
Mr. Rong, are you okay?
Tell Bowen to come to see me.
No need.
We'll go find him.
Bring your weapons.
Mr. Rong.
Are you suspecting that Ye
was killed by Bowen?
Killing someone
isn't easy for an ordinary person,
let alone killing another.
On the birthday, I told Bowen
to clean up his mess,
or Ye wouldn't show mercy.
Then Ye was killed.
Who else
could I suspect for this?
If it really is him,
I'll have to clean house myself.
If he dares to hurt Ye,
he'll dare to hurt me sooner or later.
[Psychiatry Department]
Why are we on the fourth floor?
Didn't the doctor ask you
to come to the fourth floor
for a check-up?
Xing, tell me,
do I look like a psycho?
Didn't you say
you want a full checkup?
Killing 15 people.
How many times
would he be executed for that?
Let's not talk about work.
You have all kinds of experiences.
I still have a lot to learn from you.
Seriously, do people nowadays
really brag that much?
Just ignore them.
They were going to the fourth floor.
They might be psychos.
I just came down from the fourth floor.
Mr. Rong.
I definitely wasn't talking about you.
Then why come to orthopedics?
Didn't the doctor just ask us to
come to orthopedics on the second floor?
Why come to orthopedics?
[Orthopedics Department]
Since we're here, let's have a check-up.
No, no.
Let's have a thorough check-up.
[Orthopedics Section 2]
No, I refuse.
Even if one really killed 15 people,
he can only be shot once if caught.
Li Feng.
Start confessing from the first case.
Can I start confessing
from the second case?
Mind your attitude.
[Sanjiangkou Public Security Bureau Personal Information Form]
You and Li Feng
grew up in the same village.
You are one year younger than him,
so you were childhood friends.
When you were 16,
you were raped by your uncle
from the same village.
He was a villain in your village.
Your parents were threatened by him
and didn't dare to speak up.
After Li Feng found out,
he went to him to settle the score.
During the fight,
he accidentally killed him.
He was sentenced to 12 years in prison.
This is the
first crime he committed.
I killed people
because fate was
too unfair to my wife.
After I was released,
I found out
she was forced to marry someone else.
That jerk didn't love her at all.
♪ The moon is hanging far away in the night ♪
After finding out she was raped,
not only did he not help her,
but he also beat her constantly.
He forced her to do that
♪ Lighting up the pedestrians' faces ♪
to support him.
In a fit of rage, I killed his whole family.
They were all scumbags.
♪ Why are you standing in the center of the city? ♪
Then I let her elope with me.
Li Feng constantly committed robberies
and thefts
to make a living.
During the time, he killed
♪ But I couldn't find my way home ♪
multiple innocent people.
Besides these 15 lives,
are there any others?
No.
Let me ask you another question.
Li Feng,
you were doing fine in Jiangsu,
and the police didn't track you down.
Why did you come to Sanjiangkou?
To hide from you guys.
Half a year ago,
we came to Sanjiangkou.
Then we didn't want to run anymore,
so we took over a small shop
and settled down.
One day, on the street,
I ran into an old cellmate.
He said someone hired him to kill a person.
The remuneration was 200,000 yuan.
He wanted my help and promised
to give me half of the money.
So I agreed.
I only found out later
that the target
was an old cop.
A cop?
Seemed like he was a superior official.
What was his name?
I don't remember.
I think...
I think his last name was Lu.
Chief Qi.
Keep interrogating him.
Show him the photo.
Okay.
Because of my leg injury,
I might need to go back to...
Sit down first, Yi'ang.
Sit.
What's wrong?
Is he the target?
Yes.
And then?
Did you do it?
No.
I wanted to at first
because my child is too young,
and I would need
a lot of money in the future.
I thought if I did this one job,
even if I got caught,
it'd be good to leave them some money.
Later, my wife talked me out of it.
Afterwards,
I went soft.
My cellmate
never contacted me again either.
Was this cop named Lu
killed later?
I wasn't involved. I don't know.
But I guess
my cellmate didn't do it.
He didn't have the guts.
What's your cellmate's name?
If you don't know his name,
how about his nickname?
Where did he live in Sanjiangkou?
Sir,
is the answer to this question
important to you?
Li Feng.
Look at me.
I'm asking you one last time.
Speak properly.
What's your cellmate's name?
Who hired him?
I can tell you,
but I have a request.
I want to see
my wife and child.
Someone wants to harm Chief Lu?
Grant his request.
Yi'ang.
That's against the rules.
What if they collude
to falsify statements?
I'll take responsibility for any problems.
Mr. Rong.
What's so urgent
that we can't talk about it on the phone?
In the middle of the night,
you came here in person.
I'll go get you some water.
Ren, have a seat.
Yangyang.
Go back to your room.
Just do as Mr. Rong says.
What happened, Mr. Rong?
Ye
is dead.
Who?
Ye Jian.
Captain Ye.
Dead?
How did he die?
You tell me
how he died.
Asking me?
I...
Bowen.
Mr. Rong wants to know
what you were doing last night.
I was at home.
Yangyang can prove it.
Mr. Rong,
you think I did it?
He's a cop.
Who in Sanjiangkou would dare to harm him?
Who is the most experienced at this?
Mr. Rong, I swear to God.
-If I did it...
-If swearing works,
why would we need the police?
If I did it, kill me right now.
Okay?
You think I'm not
going to do it?
Don't move.
Be careful.
Don't let it misfire.
Move away.
You move away.
Get out of the way.
Mr. Rong.
If you really don't trust me,
then shoot me right now.
Don't blame me.
You know,
I'm sick.
Mr. Rong.
Ye Jian was my bro too.
How could I do something like that?
Mr. Rong.
This whole thing is getting weirder.
That Chief Zhang
came and took Ye's position.
When he arrived, Ye died.
So,
who in Sanjiangkou
has the capability to do that?
Tell me the truth.
How did you handle
that thing half a year ago?
Mr. Rong.
Nothing will go wrong with that.
I need to know all the details.
I can't let anyone else get hurt.
Half a year ago, I put the word out
and hired a hitman
called Fei.
But he didn't dare to take the job.
Does this Fei
know about me?
No.
Do you have his contact info?
I'll contact him right now.
You don't need to worry about it.
Give the address to Jianren.
He will handle it.
Mr. Rong, Ren, are you leaving now?
Study hard.
Rongcheng Group
always has positions for young people.
Come.
Let me see you out.
No need.
We know the way.
Take care, Mr. Rong.
Why aren't you sleeping?
Brother,
between you and Mr. Rong,
there's no bad blood, right?
Don't go anywhere for now.
Especially at night.
Just stay at home.
If you really have to go somewhere,
you must let me know.
Do you hear me?
What happened?
Whatever happened
has nothing to do with you.
Just remember what I said.
How does it have nothing to do with me?
You are my brother.
[Lang Botu, Lang Bowen's younger brother]
Your business is my business.
Little kid.
You think you've grown up
and want to shoulder things for me?
Wait until you
don't have to do homework.
Then we'll talk.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Your task right now
is to study hard
and study abroad.
Don't get involved in our business.
Sir, stop asking.
If you don't grant my request,
I won't say anything.
I won't ask.
Li Feng.
Baby,
look.
That's Daddy.
I have thought of a name for the child.
He'll be named Li Feng too.
I will bring him up
stay with him all my life,
and teach him to be a good person.
Let's hit the road.
Sir.
My cellmate is called Fei,
nicknamed Scarface.
Ren.
Let me go, Ren.
Fei.
Let me ask you a few questions.
Tell the truth,
and you'll be fine.
Really?
Okay.
Does anyone else know
that I hired you to kill that person?
I didn't kill anyone.
Bro.
Listen to the question.
Listen carefully.
I remember it now.
I remember it.
Back then, I didn't dare to...
I didn't dare to do it myself.
So I...
I found a cellmate of mine,
named Li Feng.
Before doing it, we agreed
to meet at 7 p.m.
at an intersection.
But he didn't show up.
I really didn't kill anyone.
I really didn't.
I didn't.
Where is Li Feng?
I...
I don't know.
I really don't know, Bro.
I didn't trust him,
so I didn't leave him
my phone number.
You had no his contact info.
How did you contact him?
Through QQ.
I have his QQ number.
Koukou?
I have a computer at home.
QQ.
Yes.
I have a computer at home.
Typing.
Get up quickly.
Get up.
It's a misunderstanding.
Thanks for your hard work.
It's fine.
Sorry.
Ren.
Bury his mouth first.
Okay.
Okay, Bro.
Why is he still cursing?
Hello.
Li Penggai,
I need you
to take care of something.